

#### **ABOUT ME**

I have 19 years. I am an energetic and outgoing student. Curiosity and passion are the main qualities that determined most of my skills and motivated me to learn completely opposite and diverse activities like: programming, game dev, web development, music production, soccer, fitness etc.

## **EDUCATION**

2019 - 2023

National College of Informatics, Piatra-Neamt

2023 - Now

UBB, FSEGA -

Management, Cluj-

Napoca

## CONTACT

Phone

+40 783 164 678

Email

silviuiftime250@gmail.com

Adress

Str. C-tin Brâncoveanu, Nr. 56, Cluj-Napoca

# **IFTIME SILVIU**

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Unity Game Dev (C# .NET)**

2021-2022

- Forest Caretaker (self made Scripts, Design, Map, Models, Animations)
- Anti..-balls
- Experimental (a game looking like Bullet Echo)
- Metabots: Battle

Web Dev (HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6, Node, React) 2

2024

Online Bootcamp

## Volunteering

2023 - Now

• OSE (Organizația Studenților Economiști)

## **OBJECTIVES**

- My objective is to provide value to the organization in a professional manner by leveraging all my knowledge.
- I want to learn everything about the new position and fulfill my roles brilliantly.
- I aim to get the widest possible, diverse and serious experience on the labor market.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML + CSS
- JavaScript
- SQL/PostgreSQL
- Node.js
- React.js
- REST APIs
- Office (Word, Excel, PPT)
- Communication
- Teamwork

## **LANGUAGES**

English
Romanian



